Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
You know, it's still possible
for you to be good in a bad movie.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
"Sometimes I feel like I can control
(Penny:)the killer gorilla instinct
inside of me,
(Penny:)but then I see these bananas
(Penny:)and I just want to eat them
and then kill people."
(Penny:)What am I gonna do?
(Leonard:)Well, for starters,
I wouldn't eat the bananas.
Come on! This is serious.
(Leonard:)Does it at least pay well?
(Penny:)Less than I was making
at The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)What does your agent think?
(Penny:)She's thinking of taking a job
at The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)You know what,
why don't you just do it?
(Leonard:)You'll go have fun for a few weeks,
make some money,
(Leonard:)and who knows what it might lead to?
(Penny:)Okay, look, here, page 58.
(Penny:)I oil-wrestle an orangutan
in a bikini.
(Leonard:)Just to clarify, which one
of you is wearing the bikini?